christywhitman.com 2007-10-13

# Personal Empowerment - Christy Whitman

**Personal Empowerment / Christy Whitman Privacy Statement**  
Personal Empowerment / Christy Whitman respects the privacy of every individual and organization who visits our Web site(s) or responds to an online invitation. This Privacy Statement outlines our information gathering and dissemination practices for our Web site(s). Please feel free to visit our sites anonymously or as a registered guest.

 **Information Collection**  
In order to personalize your Web experience, we may at times require information from you. Due to our strong commitment to privacy, we will inform you of our information requirements before we collect it from you.

**Personal Information**  
Personal Empowerment / Christy Whitman may request personal information (e.g. user name, e-mail address) from you whether you visit our site(s) as an anonymous visitor or registered guest. We will not collect personally identifiable information unless you knowingly provide it to us.

**Business Related Information**  
Personal Empowerment / Christy Whitman will not gather business related information unless you knowingly provide it to us. This information will be used by Personal Empowerment / Christy Whitman to propose business solutions based on your requirements. Please do not submit your business information to us if you do not want it to be collected. Personal Empowerment / Christy Whitman will not use this confidential information outside of the context in which it was provided unless otherwise approved by you at time of submission.

**Anonymous Data**  
To help us understand the trends in user preferences, we may collect non-identifying information during your session as either an anonymous visitor or registered guest.   
Examples of this type of information include:

  * internet browser in use
  * type of computer operating system
  * domain name of the web site from which you linked to our site or online invitation
  * pages viewed

**Improved Services**  
Personal Empowerment / Christy Whitman uses confidential information to improve services to you to:

  * better understand your needs
  * improve our products and services
  * establish communication with you
  * recognize and better serve you in the future

**Information Access and Security**  
If you have submitted confidential information to Personal Empowerment / Christy Whitman web site, and would like that information deleted from our records, please contact Personal Empowerment / Christy Whitman.
